Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Local and Underground Press Serials TAM.758
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Rising Up Angry: Rising Up Angry, Quebec, Canada, Undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Rochester Patriot: Rocester Patriot, Rochester, NY, 1974-1981 (Box 49, Folder 2-3, Box 80, Folder 7)
- Root: Grand Rapids (GR) Peoples' Press, Grand Rapids, MI, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Rough Times: The Radical Therapist, Inc., Somerville, MA, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5, Box 49, Folder 4, Box 93)
- RT: A Journal of Radical Therapy: The Radical Therapist, Inc., Somerville, MA, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- RYM: Revolutionary Youth Movement, Los Angeles, CA, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Sabot: Sabot, Seattle, WA, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Salon: Salon, Fort Collins, CO, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Salt of the Earth: Salt of the Earth Collective, Staten Island, NY, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Salt of the Earth: Salt of the Earth, San Jose, CA, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- San Diego's Daily Impulse: Open Road Club, San Diego, CA, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 22, Box 72, Folder 9)
- San Francisco Express Times: The Trystero Company, San Francisco, CA, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- San Francisco Journal: Maurice Chuck, San Francisco, CA, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- San Francisco Star: San Francisco Star, San Francisc, CA, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Wildcat: San Francisco Wildcat, San Francisco, CA, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- San Jose Mercury: San Jose Mercury, San Jose, CA, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- San Jose Red Eye: Red Eye Media, San Jose, CA, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Saturday Evening Post Poster: The Saturday Evening Post, Indianapolis, IN, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Saturday Review: Saturday Review, Inc., New York, NY, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- SCAN Newsletter: Seattle Consumer Action Network, Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Schuylkill Bugle: The Schuylkill Bugle, St. Peters, PA, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- SCUM: SCUM, Toronto, Canada, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Seattle Sun: Seattle Sun Publishing Co., Seattle, WA, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 9, Box 28, Folder 1-3, Box 29, Box 74, Folder 1-7)
- Second City: Guild Cooperative Fellowship, Chicago, IL, 1971-1973 (Box 60, Folder 22-25, Box 80, Folder 13)
- Second Coming: Second Coming, Ypsilanti, MI, 1969-1971 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Sedition: Graphic Offensive, San Jose, CA, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Seed: Chicago Seed, Chicago, IL, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 6-12)
- Servizio Traduzione: n.p., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- A Seminar on Radicalism in American History: Radical Education Project, Ann Arbor, MI, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- SESCO News: South End Seattle Community Organization, Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Sheepshead Bay Township: Sheepshead Bay Township, Brooklyn, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Sherwood Forest: Orange County People's Press, Irvine, CA, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Shield: The Shield / Hunter College, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Ship of Fools: Ship of Fools, Westminster, MD, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Shot Tower: Shot Tower, Baltimore, MD, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 16)
- Siembra: Capitulo de Alto Manhattan de MINP-El Comite, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Silence: Silence, Boise, ID, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Sing About It: New Song Library, Northampton, MA, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Smirk: Post-Leftist Pleasure Politics: Karen Eliot, Madison, WI, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Smoke: Smoke, Ann Arbor, MI, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Social, The: The Social, circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Solidarity North West: Solidarity (North West), London, England, circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Somerville Community News: Somerville Community News, Somerville, MA, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Something Else!: Radical Education Project, Detroit, MI, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Sound: Sound, The, circa 1970s (Box 97, Folder 17)
- Soundview JR: The Society of Evergreens, Olalla, WA, 1908 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- South Baltimore Voice: South Baltimore Voice, Baltimore, MD, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- South End Press: South End Press, Boston, MA, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 11, Box 97)
- South of the River: South of the River, Pittsburgh, PA, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Southern Agitator: On Da Printing, New Orleans, LA, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Southern Communities: Southern Neighborhoods Network, Nashville, TN, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Southern Feminist Connection: SFC Collective, Winston-Salem, NC, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Southern Voice: Southern Voice, Inc, Houston, TX, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 19)
- Space City!: Space City News Collective, Houston, TX, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 1, Box 97, Folder 5)
- Spark: Party For Workers Power, Amherst, MA, 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
- Spark-Chispa: Freedom & Peace Party, New York, NY, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22, Box 76, Folder 2)
- Special Report: Behind the Walls of Massachusetts Prisons, Cambridge, MA, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Spectacular Times Pocketbook Series: Spectacular Times, London, UK, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3, Box 75, Folder 15)
- Spectator: Spectator, Bloomington, Indiana, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Spirit of Logos: Spirit of Logos, Bronx, NY, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 18)
- Spokane Natural: Spokane Natural, Spokane, WA, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 6-7)
- Sputnik Studenta: The Students' Companion: Minneapolis, MN, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- St. Louis Outlaw: St. Louis Outlaw, St. Louis, MO, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- STAR: Le Journal de Celles et Ceux Qui Revent de Toucher les Etoiles: n.p., Lyon, France, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Steeltown Monitor: -, Steeltown, CA, 1980-1989 (Box 63, Folder 23, Box 97, Folder 10)
- Still Learning to Fly Despite Missiles: Epicenter Zone, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Stony Hills: Stony Hills, New Sharon, ME, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Stop the Trial! (or) Conspiracy: Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Straight News: Straight News, Anchorage, AL, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Strategic Thought: Strategic Thought, New York, NY, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Street Paper: Youth International Party, Salt Lake City, UT, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Strike: Supervision Publications, Toronto, ON, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Strike News: American Independent Movement, New Haven, CT, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Subversive Economics Institute: Subversive Economics Institute, Victoria, Australia, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Suffolk Life Newspapers: David. J. Willmott, Riverhead, NY, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Suffolk Street Papers: Suffolk StreetPapers, Smithtown, NY, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Sun Dance: Running Dog, San Francisco, CA, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Sunday Compass: The Daily Compass Publishing Corporation, New York, NY, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Sunday Compass Magazine: The Sunday Compass, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Sunnyside Woodside Neighbor: Sunnyside-Woodside Club, American Labor Party, Long Island City, NY, 1944 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Sunrise: Tucker, St. John Irwin, Macomb, IL, circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 13)
- SWEAT: Center for Practical Education, San Francisco, CA, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Sweet Fire: Sweet Fire, Albany, NY, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Take Over: Take Over, Madison, WI, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6, Box 96, Folder 1-3)
- Talk is Cheap: TIC, Philadelphia, PA, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Target Theory: John H. Pflaum, Milwaukee, WI, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- TATblatt: Unabhangige Intiative Informationsvielfalt, Wien, Austria, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- TCB - Takin' Care of Business: TCB, Ithaca, NY, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Telos: A Journal of Radical Thought: Department of Philosophy, SUNY Buffalo, NY, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Thistle: Alternative News Collective at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, MA, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Three Village Herring: The Three Village Herring, East Setauket, NY, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Thunderbolt: The National States Rights Party, Birmingham, AL, 1961-1966 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Times Now: Now Associates INC., Coconut Grove, FL, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Toronto Clarion: Toronto Clarion Publishing Ltd., Toronto, Canada, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 21, Box 63, Folder 26)
- Traduction: Comite Revolutionnaire Culture Agissante, France, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Tribune: Tribune Publications, Ltd, London, England, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 16, Box 97, Folder 20)
- Tribune: Pacific Tribune Publishing Association / Canadian Tribune Publishing Association, Vancouver, Canada, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
- Tribune de Geneve: Tribune de Geneve, Geneva, Switzerland, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- True People's Power: True People's Power, Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Two-Bit Times / Newsstand News: The Two-Bit Times, New York, NY, Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Työmies eteenpäin: Työmies Society, Superior, WI, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Ukrainian-American: Slavic-American Publishing Corp., New York, NY, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Underground: Thomas de Baggio, Arlington, VA, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Underground Rag: Thomas de Baggio, Arlington, VA, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- United Front News: United Front of Cairo, IL, Cairo, IL, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- University of Illinois Bulletin: University of Illinois, Urbana, IL, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 15, Box 93)
- Uppercut: Uppercut, Liege, Belgium, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- UPS News Service: Underground Press Syndicate / Free Ranger Tribe, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16-18)
- Urban Underground: MDS Collective, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- US Farm News: US Farmers Association, Denison, IA, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- UWM Post: University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, Milwaukee, WI, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Valley Alliance: The Valley Alliance, Kalamazoo, MI, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Vermont Commons: Vermont Commons, Waitsfield, VT, 2006-2009 (Box 97, Folder 1-2)
- Vermont Freeman: Hanksville Associates Incorporated, Huntington, VT, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6-13, Box 13, Folder 10, Box 23, Folder 1-11, Box 24, Folder 4-6)
- View from the Bottom: Underground Press Service, New Haven, CT, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 10-11)
- Virginian: Lacy Jeffreys, Newport News, VA, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Virginity: Virginity, circa 1980s (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Voice of Grass Roots Women: Coalition of Grass Roots Women, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Vortex: Underground Press Syndicate, Lawrence, KS, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Vorwärts, Berliner Volksblatt: M. Bading, Berlin, Germany, 1932-1933 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Vrijbrief: Stichting Vrijwilligerscentrale, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Walrus: Walrus, Champaign, IL, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Washington Free Press: Washington Free Community, Inc., Washington, DC, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 5, Box 63, Folder 29)
- Washington Park Spirit: Washington Park Spirit, Inc., Albany, NY, 1972-1975 (Box 79, Folder 1-6)
- Water Tunnel: Water Tunnel Cooperative, State College, PA, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Waves: Northwest Passage, Inc., Seattle, WA, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Waves: The Sound Alternative: WAVES, Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Wayne Reply: Wayne State University, Detroit, MI, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- We The People: We the People, Madison, WI, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23, Box 70, Folder 12, Box 72, Folder 12-13)
- Weather Report: Southwest Texas State University, San Marcos, TX, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Weekly News: New York State Council of Senior Citizens et al., New York, NY, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Weekly Register: Nuneaton Newspapers, Ltd., Nuneaton, England, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
- WESPAC Newsletter: Westchester People's Action Coalition, White Plains, NY, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- West Brooklyn Peace and Freedom Newsletter: Peace and Freedom Party, Brooklyn, NY, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- West Side Neighborhood Rally: West Side Child Care Council, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- West Side Torch: West Side Organization, Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Westchester Historian: Westchester County Historical Society, Elmsford, NY, 1990-1994 (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
- Westchester Historical Happenings: Westchester County Historical Society, Elmsford, NY, 1983-1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Western Voice: Western Voice Collective, Vancouver, Canada, 1973-1975 (Box 78, Folder 1-4)
- What Community Leaders Should Know: Northeast Community Organization / Institute for Urban Research, Morgan State University, Baltimore, MD, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- What's Happening?: What's Happening / The Lower East Side News, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- What's Left: Radical Information Project, Denver, CO, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- What's Left in Boston: What's Left, Boston, MA, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Whippersnapper: Underground Press Syndicate, McConnellsburg, PA, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- White Lightning: White Lightning, New York, NY, 1972-1975 (Box 42, Folder 1-2, Box 25, Folder 11, Box 36, Folder 8-9, Box 65, Folder 4-5)
- Wichita: Wichita Area Chamber of Commerce, Wichita, KS, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Wild Raspberry: Wild Raspberry / Perry White, Hartford, CT, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Wildcat: Wildcat Press, Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 13, Box 97, Folder 15)
- Wildcat: San Diego County Workers Committee, San Diego, CA, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Wildcat Report: Wildcat Report, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Willamette Alliance, The: Oregon Coalition of Alternative Human Services, Portland, Or, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Willamette Bridge: Bridgeworks, Inc., Portland, Or, 1968-1971 (Box 77, Folder 1-6)
- Wisconsin Patriot: The Wisconsin Alliance, Madison, Wi, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Words of Liberation, Words of Love: A.W.O.L. (A World of Liberation), Lynbrook, NY, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Worker Magazine: Freedom of the Press Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Working People's News:, New York, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Working People's Voice: n.p, New York, NY, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Yellow Dog Comics: Print Mint, Inc., Berkeley, CA, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Yellow Rag: Jester of Columbia, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Yipster Times: Youth International Party News Service, New York, NY, 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 14, Box 95, Folder 1)
- You Heard It Through...the Grapevine: Chicago District Official Bulletin: n.p., Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Young Communist: Revolutionary Student Brigade National Newspaper: Revolutionary Student Brigade, Chicago, IL, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Zenger: Madison Alternative Press Syndicate, Madison, WI, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Zine Orgy: Zine Orgy Editors, Seattle, WA, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Zine World: Zine World, Murfreesboro, TN, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Zone 23 Getting it Together: Zone 23 Getting it Together, Baltimore. MD, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
- ΣΚΟΛΕ: National Coalition on Alternative Community Schools, Albany, NY, 1988-1989 (Box 75, Folder 8)